You have a lot of retribution, a karma in the East.
Whatever you put out, you'll come back to you, and more.
And one says you can guide people, but if you are, you're only doing so in the sense that you're an instrument of God's will.
And it reminds me of Yossen, which I've been reading a lot.
Whether you warn them or you warn them not, they will not believe.
So people who are going to believe will believe and people aren't going to believe aren't going to believe.
You may be there as an intermediary, you may be the first one to stick the core in in their hand,
but it's not in their heart to believe it, they're not going to believe it.
So basically, yeah, all power is to God.
Charity shall go to the fore, who are persecuted because of their belief and trapped.
Those who aren't aware, those who aren't aware may think that they are rich due to their honorable character.
You can recognize them by certain signs.
They never annoy the people by begging.
Any charity you give God is fully aware of.
Those who give charity by name and by name,
secretly and publicly their recommends with the Lord.
They have no idea fear nor will they leave.
In Morocco, there are people who bother you
with called charity, but it's their professional beggars.
I mean, they may not even be poor.
And I vividly remember one woman in Marrakash
who could cry and will come up and, you know,
Whether you know whether her husband was lazy and they've had money and
Just said go out and beg if you want something and they really had money
Where as you just see people they're just sitting they're citing
Something from the core and not even thinking about charity and people would throw that money
It's a good illustration
I see one night. Some of them died and they found the message is stuck with the Bible. They were proficient in records. And those were the music.
So it's basically more about the laws of security. People who are persecuted because of their belief in trans...
[ Inaudible ]
So I just --
Again, saying that charity is a good thing and it's one of the five cards and it explains a little bit more about it.
[ Inaudible ]
These three lines are about the security and the core
who are persecuted for their belief.
They track.
What is the, what is that mean in here?
I think.
They got to emigrate to another terrorist war, you think?
Where they get on our own.
They're not even a business.
Something about drugs and their followers is just a different.
I just think of all the people who I've seen chanting and
And one man, I remember, was a beautiful,
and he had his most beautiful voice.
And he would just stand in the street and recite from the
audience blind.
And he didn't seem like he ever wanted charity.
People would see him and they would get him what he wanted.
He didn't seem like he cared enough.
You just felt really good when you gave something to him.
And then there were these professional beggars who would just go around and
They just go around and you didn't know if they were really, you know, I suppose if you
were a tourist and you didn't live there very long, you wouldn't really know for sure.
On the other hand, if you've ever been to Marrakash, you know that if you feed all the
beggars of Marrakash, you'll be able to beg yourself.
In Morocco and in the East, begging is not illegal.
I mean, you can actually-- it's actually something
that people do professional.
So I think these three verses are making a distinction.
Here you can't just go around and ask people for money
for a handout.
You can send it in Bummore, Francine, or something like that.
It's really-- you can be arrested for vagrancy,
or something like that.
That's right.
[INAUDIBLE]
It's so nice.
[LAUGHTER]
[INAUDIBLE]
[ Inaudible ]
Just the predominance of begging, all right?
It's not a very predominant in this country compared to it.
It's just not very predominant to see people standing around on this three year, you know,
with all of them have the assistance to work there.
And you'll see another guy when he's showing his stump off,
you know, the show back, you know, no leg.
Make sure you see it, you know, or somebody walks up to you
and shows you that he doesn't have any arms.
And he wants to-- it's a different--
[INTERPOSING VOICES]
[INAUDIBLE]
So it's really the people who are-- who are personally
because of what they believe that deserve--
deserve a charity the most. You can recognize it by their signs. They never
annoy people by making. These fingers can be very much of a nuisance.
[ Inaudible ]
I remember I was diving in the community.
I was the most part of the people who lived in the city.
Licks are like.
I was not in the next, that was put by a mother's psyche.
Maybe a mother.
We had human beings putting in their law.
And there's a piece of crowded.
And I must have had like one big ocean.
One of them, where are they going?
Not to what's successful.
They're spitting into very fast, but no, no, no, no.
Of course, it's stunning that I have an American.
Then I get them to the X- Tok.
And the driver goes very fast.
And the toilet before, you put a stinner out of it, correct?
And then they go really fast.
And we get to the divorces for about a minute.
And then he'll slow down because of the crowd.
Just a minute, and he'll at 12 again.
He'll be around for an hour after the picture.
Very fast.
The problems.
I mean, they can win marathon and make millions of dollars in this country.
But there's nothing to fix a miracle.
And now he needs to have lots of people.
He put the morning chair.
[laughter]
I didn't give him any hand for him.
Yeah, he was that kind.
He was that kind of big kid.
No more members in Egypt, put the morning prisoners in there.
a little bit. So I think you're just going to be doing this. It's like a big thing to see. You know, you want to call it. You can't just go. You're playing a musical instrument. Well, that's in your street entertainer. You just walk around and sleep. I got a diamond on the corner. Five dollars to it. And it's almost like it was in the same place. And I don't know if they have, they have books.
[ Inaudible ]
Francisco's point of people who are actually in potatoes,
like we said, very talented.
They taught me today.
Some of them were shocked from a hundred feet up
into a pair of water, you know, just a little.
(laughing)
I mean, they're risking the light,
but they really have to fail.
(laughing)
Some musicians.
Musicians.
And.
You know, I've been for territories and my own self-interiority.
And so.
(static)